<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
<channel>
<atom:link href='https://yetibot.com/' rel='self' type='application/rss+xml'/>
<title>
Yetibot
</title>
<link>
https://yetibot.com/
</link>
<description>
Docs and blog posts for Yetibot
</description>
<lastBuildDate>
Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:57:04 +0000
</lastBuildDate>
<generator>
clj-rss
</generator>
<item>
<guid>
https://yetibot.com/blog/2018-11-11-yeticast-0/
</guid>
<link>
https://yetibot.com/blog/2018-11-11-yeticast-0/
</link>
<title>
Yeticast #0: Bug fix for subexpression evaluation
</title>
<description>
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the 0th yeticast!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode we fix issue &lt;a href='https://github.com/yetibot/yetibot/issues/784'&gt;#784&lt;/a&gt; in which subexpression evaluation was very broken due to recent improvements in error handling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the not-so-great quality. It ended up being about 720p even though I had done a few test runs with much higher resolution. It apparently matters what order in Zoom you:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;share desktop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;start camera&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;press record&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'll research better screencasting options, or just figure out Zoom's quirks before I record another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also quite a bit longer than expected, but I'm publishing it anyway to force myself to do better next time. In the middle I realize I didn't actually know how to fix the bug, which felt awkward, but thankfully through some poking around in the REPL I recovered and figured it out. Fast forward to around minute 35 if you want to skip to where I actually figure out what I'm doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;video-responsive&quot;&gt;   &lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/sc5s1t2sFWg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let me know if you have feedback or requests on what to screencast next in the comments. I'd like to cast a dev setup along with other features and bug fixes that make it easier for new contributors to get started.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<pubDate>
Sun, 11 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000
</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
https://yetibot.com/blog/2018-03-24-launch/
</guid>
<link>
https://yetibot.com/blog/2018-03-24-launch/
</link>
<title>
Yetibot.com Launch
</title>
<description>
&lt;p&gt;Yetibot finally has a site!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href='https://github.com/yetibot/yetibot.github.io'&gt;source on GitHub&lt;/a&gt; here if you're so inclined. It's powered by &lt;a href='http://cryogenweb.org/'&gt;Cryogen&lt;/a&gt;, the Clojure-based static site generator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the goals with launching the site was to have inline interactive Yetibot examples that uses the GraphQL API on the public Yetibot instance to evaluate! See the &lt;a href='/user-guide'&gt;User Guide&lt;/a&gt; to check out the interactive examples in the docs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The site and docs are pretty bare bones but we'll improve it over time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<pubDate>
Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000
</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
